Good afternoon, people.
Today is the day we play Binding of Isaac.
And we get drunk.
The best combination of all time.
Probably not, it's gonna go horribly.
But we'll see.
If anything goes wrong, it's not me.
It's the Boos, okay?
Ah, yeah.
I got myself some moonshine.
Thought it was fitting.
I'm playing Red Dead Redemption now.
What's up, people?
Are you excited?
Have you seen the Silent Hill 2 movie that dropped a couple of months ago?
No, I haven't.
Is it good?
I gotta watch that.
I was thinking about Silent Hill today.
Both blind and drunk.
No, no, trust that the drunkenness will cure the blindness.
It'll be good.
Sometimes you need to think less to think more.
I'm Oliver.
I'm here for wisdom.
Or what do you call it?
Wise words.
And insights that you can't get anywhere else.
I got something in the wrong part of my throat.
Anyway, what's my favorite game?
I'm glad you asked.
Check this out.
Well, you can look at the... Hold on, let me actually link it to you.
The backlog is up, finally.
You can see what my favorite game is there.
Now I will say those, you know, enjoyment ratings are subject to change.
I kinda just threw them in real fast.
I gotta think about the enjoyment ratings a bit more, you know?
To
answer your question, World of Warcraft Classic, baby.
That's the best game of all time.
I didn't watch the new Subnautica 2 trailer.
Maybe I should.
But I am excited about the game in general.
I wanna play more Exotica.
Subnautica.
Ah, man.
Purple J, I am using Claude code.
I use the pro subscription, so I think I pay...
I think it's $10 a month or something?
And you have a certain... I mean, you probably need more than that if you do it full time, right?
This is a hobby thing I do.
But I would suggest you...
If you wanna use something, probably that.
But yeah.
I mean, if you're actually using it all day every day, you should probably get something with a bit more...
With a higher limit, right?
I'm totally doing this as a personal hobby thing, just for fun.
Fucking around, basically, right?
Yeah.
I use it in VS Code, as a plugin.
Sync it up to GitHub, you know?
You can even look at the... or make it...
You can write your own sort of... what do you call it?
Suggestions on GitHub, right?
Or, like, you can address the issues there and then the thing will take care of it.
It's amazing.
I'm using Burcell to host it.
With Superbase.
Mostly Svelte and stuff.
And some Tailwind for styling.
This song reminds me of Zelda Twilight Princess every time.
Ooh!
That makes me excited for Zelda Twilight Princess now.
If that game has music like this, then I'm excited about it.
Because this is exactly my jam.
You did that intentionally?
You bastard.
You know what?
I will actually say the music does also remind me a little bit of Majora's Mask.
Slightly.
Not entirely, but slightly.
Wait, there's Claude for Unity?
That sounds cool.
What does that do?
Oh, it's just for coding and Unity?
Or can it do, like, 3D stuff?
Or... that sounds exciting.
Sounds like fun.
Twilight Princess supposed to be the best after Ocarina of Time and Majora's Mask?
I will be the judge of that?
No, I won't.
I'm not the authority on anything.
I am the authority on my own opinions, though.
But yeah.
You don't do 3D in Unity as far as I'm aware?
Wait, what?
You don't?
Oh, wait, no, nevermind.
I mixed it up.
I thought you said... What's the other... I thought you meant Blender for some reason.
Unity is the game development engine.
That's right.
My bad.
Sorry.
I totally misunderstood what you meant.
I was like, what?
What do you mean?
Claude in Blender, you know?
But you could probably do it nowadays, I don't know.
What's with the voice change?
Wait, what voice change?
Oh my god, I thought I had left on this voice change and nobody said anything.
Is my voice not normal right now?
Am I okay?
Is there a voice problem or...?
Like you had some mucus in your throat?
Oh.
I mean, I probably do a little bit.
It's allergy season now.
So I'm gonna, you know, have to mute myself regularly and blow my nose, because shit sucks.
Can you make new different voices for voice acting that you switched to?
No, no, no.
So when I do voice acting in the games, just for fun, you know, when I play, I don't use any sort of filters or anything.
Sometimes I'll put something in my mouth, you know, like, what's going on right now, people?
You know, a simple thing like that mixes things up on the spot, right?
You may have noticed that for... what's that guy called in Silksong?
I don't want to actually say it.
I don't want to spoil anything for anyone, but you know what I mean, right?
Yeah, that guy, exactly.
What voice would a seasonal have?
I don't know, something dark and sinister, I guess, because he is kind of a demon.
He's very demon.
Probably similar to the voice, yeah, exactly.
Oh, man.
Some acesling today.
I think I'm gonna go on an acesle detox today.
It's time to change it up a little bit.
I had a lot of acesle.
Was it last time or the time before that?
I was going a little crazy with acesle.
Acesle detox coming up again.
You got to regularly, you know, cleanse your body of the acesle.
Solar system.
That's right, baby.
Solar system all the way.
Drunk solar system style.
That's like a horrible idea.
But guys, I will actually do the first run as solar system.
I don't know why.
I just feel like this is it.
I can do it.
The first run solar system.
If I fail, I'm not going to try again.
I'm going to resist the temptation to immediately press spacebar and redo.
I will give it one attempt today.
One.
And it'll be the first run.
And boy, will I succeed.
Because I'm really gonna try.
Like real try hard mode has been activated for this.
Oh, man.
OK, let's do this.
Oh, wait, I missed.
I missed time.
Oh,
the solar system.
OK.
I got myself up here.
Oh, OK.
OK.
We got this.
Oh, that sound.
Oh, it was just my solar system initializing.
Solar system initialized.
OK, let's go.
Believe in me, people.
I can do it.
I know I can.
Look at that.
That was amazing.
Good stuff.
Now, oh, a book room.
Now, that's exciting.
We are, of course, lost right now.
We have a curse and it's not great.
Hold on.
I need to adjust my desk's position.
Adjust humidity and pressure in my room.
Temperature.
There we go.
Nice.
Everything has been correctly configured.
I'm like a lizard.
I need very precise environmental statistics to be comfortable.
Let's go.
I'm kidding, by the way.
I don't have all those options.
Oh, I can fly.
Right.
That's a boon.
We're out in the boonies with that one.
That's a bit scary.
How did that hit me now?
Come on, son.
Oh, man, he's about to explode.
Nice.
Good.
I'm going to wait for my fly here.
Patient.
Patient run here.
Oh, that's massive, though.
Except it ain't.
I can't see the map.
Oh, no.
OK, I'll save it for next floor.
It's OK.
There we go.
I believe, guys, positivity is all we need and then we can do it.
I'm trying to stay positive.
I'm managing.
Come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, OK.
That was actually amazing the way I did that.
OK, we're losing some HP here.
It's OK.
It's part of the process.
All right.
Now we are still lost.
I don't know where I am.
I missed some doors to the south for sure.
Oh, I keep pressing shift, I guess.
I think I'm going to buy this, except I can't.
Maybe I can.
Yeah, I'm taking that.
I think it's worth just for the survival.
I think we're looping back around.
Hold on, I got to blow my nose real quick.
This is like the first proper day of the year where I really feel the allergies, you know?
It's a bad omen.
Man, spiders are the worst when you play a solo system.
OK, that was good.
What do we got here?
A beggar.
I may as well spawn him.
Oh, he takes hearts.
Well, well, well.
We got money now, too.
Let me go back to that shop.
Question mark card.
Pokey go.
Chance at the start of each new room to summon a permanently charmed monster.
That could be super helpful for me because... Wait a sec, what's this?
No, I don't like that.
Because I lack damage, right?
So if I can gain an ally, that could be huge.
I need three more coins.
Maybe it's doable.
Maybe if I destroy this man.
But I need to ensure some healing first.
Chance to heal half a red heart each time you clear a room.
That's good!
I like that.
Let's do this first.
Oh!
Damn!
OK, this is my shot.
That was good damage.
Beautiful.
We even gained some healing there just by defeating the boss.
This is useless for me, I guess, but I'm going to go give this guy some hearts now because we can heal.
Oh, you're not going to give me money?
What?
Dude, what is this scammery?
One more.
Yeah, yeah.
What's that?
Unidentified?
That was not good.
I could go blow up some fires, I guess.
Or look for secrets.
Actually, let's do this.
Aw, man.
Nothing.
This room we didn't go into.
Come
on.
Good.
Pop up, my friend.
Wait, how did the other guy die just now?
Wait, there's a tinted rock!
I thought they couldn't spawn in these challenges.
Uh, yeah, I'll take that.
There's this bag up here.
Now, what about secret rooms?
I need one more coin.
This can be done, right?
It's hard when I can't see the map here.
OK, I got one bomb left.
Oh, right, there's this!
I forgot about that.
Book of Revelations!
Soulheart!
Oh, that's big!
That's a good one.
Book of Belial.
This one is useless for me.
So I'm taking this.
Never mind, I'm not going to buy that item.
Yes, I am going to buy that item.
We're going to get one coin somewhere.
Trust that we can do it.
I need to hit multiple things with this bomb to maximize my chances.
Maybe also a spot where I can destroy like a poop and get a chance of destroying a wall, you know, at the same time.
So where could we do that?
Or maybe a... Oh, maybe this guy actually.
This is probably my best bet right here.
No!
He didn't spawn anything for me.
Oh man, am I... OK, that's fine.
We save our money for the next shot.
Who knows?
We're probably going to find something even better.
Oh yeah, my friends.
Come with me.
OK, we got poops.
I don't care.
Oh, wait a minute.
I should be using this every time.
For some reason I looked at it and thought, oh yeah, I have a Bible.
But I don't.
Oh, that's also good.
What do I like more?
I think I... No, I don't like this because I have flies on my friends, right?
It's wasted.
Oh, but actually, dude.
OK, wait, I'm going to do this.
Yes.
Give me... convert.
Then we take this.
No, no, we take this again.
Dude, we can go back and forth between these two.
This is insane.
This is the ultimate set up.
Oh, close one.
Yeah, you're my friends now.
You're my friends.
Let's go in here.
Convert.
And now we take the other item so we can get more soul hearts and then we keep converting.
Amazing.
Actually, I should probably go to the boss with all these flies.
Man, the way they fly together is kind of neat.
I like that.
Oh, this asshole.
The flies are going to be so helpful here.
Oh, good night.
Bandages for me.
Man, that was brutal.
He got dismantled.
Let's go this way.
Uh-oh.
Shit.
Jim, hagalas.
Hagalas.
What's that?
Oh, more flies for my fly army.
I like that.
Copy his head.
Hey, more flies!
This may actually be better for me.
Activating replaces the floor boss with a harbinger.
Do I keep this, though?
I'm actually pretty torn here.
I am.
And what is this?
All more soul hearts?
We take that.
You know what that means?
That means we're going to go back and grab the converter, baby.
That's up here.
We're going to keep converting.
Think about it like this.
The more we convert, the better...
What do you call it?
The better devil deals are going to become, right?
Now, is this door open?
It's not.
Okay.
Let's check out... this.
You want coins?
I can give you some HP.
Maybe that's enough for now?
Let's go down here.
Ah, shit!
I was there already.
I messed up.
That was bad.
Not bad.
I think we're good, though.
Oh, I can't convert, then!
No!
No more rooms!
Sharp plug!
Using an uncharged item will exchange half a red heart for each missing charge segment?
Uses red hearts first.
Stops working when Isaac is at half health.
Oh!
I guess I could do that.
Using an uncharged item...
for each missing charge segment.
Wait, hold on, what?
Oh, using it, okay.
Sick!
We take that, we move on.
The plays here, though, are out of control.
Maybe I go back to the gambling place and place a bomb.
No, I don't have a bomb, okay.
Moving on.
Wait, I could have used Takalas to destroy that whole room.
Ah, that's fine.
I'll save it.
Okay.
Let's kill these fools.
I can sit over here and chill.
Convert, or actually, it's not a conversion, it's... I don't know, summoning?
Creation.
Son, why are you standing still over there?
What is this?
Weird.
Monkey Paul spawns a black heart when Isaac is reduced to half a heart.
This trinket is consumed after triggering three times?
Ah, that's a good synergy.
Oh, okay, it's a trinket.
Man, ah, I can't... I can.
Why didn't it spawn a... Oh, because we gotta go down to half a red heart.
So if we find a donation machine, that's gonna be good.
This is the plan now.
I don't have any money anyway, but I guess I could take a look.
Okay.
What was that one?
Nightlight?
That's pretty good, actually.
Slowing enemies down.
Okay, so I'm definitely gonna need to play a little defensive here.
I need to shoot the boob.
Oh my god, you gotta be kidding me.
Okay.
I think I go here first.
Wish I could convert even more now.
I've had a school bag.
Nice.
If I... wait, if I use my Bible now... Hold on.
Or not Bible, Book of Revelations.
No, let's see here.
Uncharged item will exchange half a red heart for each missing charge segment.
So if I do this now, I'm gonna be at half a red heart and I'm gonna trigger a black heart, right?
What?
Spawns a black heart when Isaac is reduced to half a heart?
Oh, maybe it's like in total, so my blue hearts need to go as well.
What the fuck, man?
That wasn't in the contract.
Well, it was, but, you know, it wasn't the fine print.
Hard to see.
Good.
Solid.
I'm getting a lot of hearts, though.
This is the good thing.
That didn't need to happen.
Oh, not spiders.
Just keep moving and we should be okay.
Grants an increase to all stats when health active item is at full charge.
Oh, nah.
Oh, they're friends.
There we go, blood donation.
Ah, wait, I don't need that, though.
Because I figured out it doesn't work like that.
Let me do this first.
Spawn that, give me that.
Maybe I destroy everything in here.
Just for fun.
Kind of want to try and use it against the boss.
Because apparently, kills or removes the armor from many stone enemies.
Wait, who are stone enemies?
I haven't seen a single enemy that has armor.
At least I don't think so.
Yeah, let's just leave, I guess.
I don't know if this monkey paw is any good.
I'll take this instead.
I don't think that's doing anything for me.
I could destroy this room with hagalas.
And there was nothing.
I was hoping for something because there were so many rocks.
The little fly is very helpful.
Nice, good stuff.
Wait, is that the second one?
Yeah, it is.
Block shots, deals contact damage and fires charm shots.
Sick!
That almost never happens.
Can we go further with that?
What is the next level?
Charm tears, chases enemies and deals contact damage.
And then, is there more?
There is.
Bigger familiar.
Increased damage and has a chance to drop hearts when killing enemies.
Wow.
Okay, well, we definitely got to go in here.
Spirit of the night!
That's useless for me.
Missing page two.
Black heart, that's good.
Deals room-wide damage upon taking a hit.
Yeah, that's gonna help me.
Unironically.
Like, a lot.
It's gonna help me a lot.
Yeah, this does nothing for me at all.
Good stuff.
Cheers.
Shit, I'm leaving a stain on my table here.
Hold on.
Condensation.
Alright, brother.
Show me what's good.
Show me a good time.
Take me by the hand and guide me.
Puberty.
Oh, I want to destroy these so bad.
Can we somehow?
I don't think we can.
Oh, crap.
Alright, bombs, you're gonna have to do this.
I trust in you.
Come on, come on.
There we go.
I think I'll keep this one.
Sponsor... Blood donation machine!
Oh, wait, that's a synergy with what I just got.
You know what?
I could put this down in a boss arena, take myself down to one, and deal damage that way.
It sounds really dumb, but it's doable.
Or in a room, I guess, a normal room.
You know?
It makes sense.
Let's do it here.
Fuck it.
I feel good about this.
Huh?
Ahh!
It's not red hearts.
I was fooled again!
God damn it.
Oh,
that was a black heart.
Right, right, right.
I thought it just triggered.
I was so confused.
Boss is here.
Revelate, and I have one bomb I can use for something.
I'll save it.
It's the Fallen.
No way.
Okay, good, good dodge.
Get in there.
Okay, he's gonna split.
I think these guys also do lasers?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, man.
Jesus!
Wow!
Oh, man.
Oi, oi, oi.
Nice.
What do we got?
Guppy's color.
That's gonna take us to two out of three.
A chance to be revived?
That is nice.
Now, let's see what we can get in here.
Guppy's tail!
That takes us to three out of three.
If we want to...
Here we go!
Take one heart of self-damage to gain a tear-up?
Oh, that's useless.
Subsequent uses in the same room.
Ah, that's horrible.
I'll take that.
So, what does that do?
Guppy's...
I guess I can't read about it, right?
It's just...
I don't know what it does.
That's the problem.
Following Familia that generates a trail of damage and creep, I think I want this as well.
The more help I can get, the better, right?
I don't have any way of damaging enemies.
I need all the assistance.
Okay, thank God we got some healing here.
Just a little bit, though.
Maybe I'll leave some damage and creep down there for them.
Ah, it's too risky to get in there.
Here we go, here we go.
Enjoy that creep.
Creep for y'all.
Good stuff.
More healing.
Ah, let's go.
Dammit.
I can't believe it.
I gotta be a little careful.
I only have three red hearts left.
Man, the creep is gonna be so helpful.
Against enemies that, you know, don't fly, I guess.
Horrible item.
Creep for y'all.
I'm gonna make a creep perimeter.
That's right, follow me.
Follow me.
Come here.
Dude, the creep is actually sick.
I think I've been sleeping on that a bit in the past.
Okay, I think I'm gonna buy that.
I could also store red hearts.
No, it's an active.
We don't like that.
I'll take this.
I'm not gonna go step.
Absolutely not.
I will destroy this wall, though.
Told ya.
What's happening in here?
Nice!
Dude, I have a feeling.
It was a bad feeling.
What is the other one?
Uh, Mom's toenail.
Toenails and taxes.
The two favorite things in my life.
God, I love it.
Come here.
Say, ahh.
Super Envy.
These Envy's of all the friends I have here.
Let me just thread the needle there.
Oh, God.
Yeah, the creep is not doing a lot here.
And split him up.
Pretty good aim, I will say.
Yes.
Very good.
And that was that.
That's all she wrote.
Time to move on.
Should I grab that?
Actually, I'm gonna go to the machine real quick.
I'm gonna optimize the shit out of this.
I need every single bit of help I can get here.
And that should do it.
Ooh, nice.
Ten coins.
Now I can heal up.
This is a double.
Double trouble.
Actually, I could go in here.
Let me check that out.
Uh, ooh.
We need one more puberty.
This one is undiscovered.
Speed up, tears down.
That's good for me!
Bob's curse, more bombs!
Yay!
Massive room.
Absolutely massive room.
So happy I went in there.
I have a feeling right now for Cowbell.
Right over here.
You'll see.
Uh, probably not.
Actually, do this!
Oh no, it's gonna take a lot.
Oh, that hurts!
Oh, my bomb budget!
I can't afford that.
Okay, I'm moving on.
Maybe I'll take the mushroom.
Uh, gain a random passive mushroom effect.
I wonder if that will be beneficial to me?
Even though I'm not using, uh, you know, tears to shoot.
Maybe it can somehow help me.
I don't know what mushroom effects there are.
Moving on.
Hold on, I gotta, I gotta speed up a little bit here.
Cheers, guys.
Hope you're having a wonderful Saturday.
That's what I'm talking about!
Bring it on.
I'm gonna leave creep for y'all.
There you go, walk on that.
Walk on my creep.
Or I will creep when you walk.
Wait, what?
Boi!
Soon we'll be able to spawn another heart.
And it's gonna be good.
I'm gonna creep up the entire floor here.
There you go.
Oh, shit.
Creep is really good against the little guys.
Well, shit.
I don't like this shop very much.
When would I ever want this?
Link to tunnel openings.
Maybe I can use them to dodge attacks?
Is that stupid?
Probably, right?
I'm gonna grab this.
And that's it for now.
Perhaps I'll come back for that bomb.
We'll see how it goes.
Oh, bombs.
Wait, what?
How do I...
I gotta destroy this.
Ah, I take the hit.
I take the hit.
Locky Penny.
Nice.
Creep for y'all.
I think I'm getting better at utilizing that stuff.
Yup.
I had a feeling that was gonna be a laser.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what does that jump?
I've never seen that guy before.
That's a new variety.
Circle of death.
Come on.
Walk into it.
Good.
This is so evil.
Actually, they can't do anything.
This is my home turf.
How good is that?
That's fine.
He wants coins.
I may actually give it to him.
Reveals that.
Ooh, massive.
Secret discovered.
Four bombs on hand.
Things are looking good.
Yeah, see?
The secret place is nestled in between a bunch of rooms here.
Exactly according to my theories.
Sick.
We're getting rich here.
We can give that beggar a bunch of money.
Make his day.
Perhaps even week.
I must just sit here a bit.
When we wait for them to charge, like that, and then we go in again.
The strategies.
Okay, I'll do it.
Okay.
No problem.
Yeah, my friends!
Now, I am getting a little low on HP here.
Ideally, I would love to have had 16 times the HP right now.
But I don't.
It's okay.
We're going to have to live with it.
This room again.
Don't mind if I do.
Makes no difference to me.
Another lucky penny.
Maybe that will change the tide, you know, in this run.
Being ultra lucky.
Amazing!
Okay, it's going really well.
It's going really well.
Don't jinx it.
War!
I'm going into battle and I require your strongest flies.
Okay, that's fine.
What are you doing, sir?
You can't even step in my creep, unfortunately, because he's a flying bitch.
He just got hit by his own bomb.
Oh, there you are.
It's going to take a while.
We're going to be patient.
Dude, if he charges into the fires...
This is the strategy.
I go down here.
Come to me and then charge me.
No, no, no.
I need you to...
Okay, maybe he's not going to actually go where I am.
He's just doing his own thing.
Okay, he's no longer on the horse.
This is good news.
Which means he can walk in my creep.
Follow me!
I know you want to follow me.
Beautiful.
Another ball of bandages!
Okay, it's got to be rigged.
Oh my God, it's a little creature now.
With flowers in her hair.
And lasers in their shoes.
I'm getting closer to the rumored four.
Level four.
Okay, 41 coins.
We move on.
Okay.
I'm not ready.
I'm ready.
76.2% demon as well.
What an oddly specific number.
I wonder why that is.
Yeah!
Yeah, I love my little buddy!
This is going to be great.
Okay, okay.
Now that we have a bunch of familiars, we're finally going to test this.
But wait, I'm going to give this guy some money.
Oh my God!
I think this has something to do with my luck, guys.
It has to be luck.
Luck affects these beggars.
I'm going to note it down.
I'm so convinced.
Luck majorly affects beggars.
Because I am mega lucky and I am, you know, really making it work with the beggars.
Okay, watch.
Oh, wait a minute.
It released a poison cloud.
Maybe that's what that is.
I can use it as like an offensive, static thing in the arena, you know?
But that seems hardly like amazing.
Seems kind of meh, meh, meh, you know?
But I guess it could come in handy.
If you are playing something like what I'm playing.
Doubles bombs, I like it.
Mom?
I'm scared!
Kill!
Good.
Okay, there we go.
I think I'm actually just going to go in here.
Mom!
I believe, guys.
I believe.
We're going to put creep in the center if she's going to stomp, right?
It's stomping.
Yeah, stand in my creep.
Yes, it's working!
It's the way.
Yeah, you like my creep?
You like my creep?
We're actually doing it.
We just got to play patient here.
Okay, that was bad.
That was bad.
At least my little helper is helping.
Okay, there we go.
It's going slowly.
Actually, maybe my best bet at doing damage is on these side thingies over here.
Like here, you know?
Oh, shit, I didn't even see that.
It's a fucking DPS race.
Yeah, okay.
That's fine.
We're chilling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good, good, good, good.
Focus.
Step on my creep.
Yeah!
Finally!
We did it!
First step complete.
Oh, very good, very good.
We got tears and this is useless.
That's unbelievably useless.
I forgot we cannot go back.
I done goofed here.
We have to move on.
Shit!
Big goof!
Damn it!
Just means we got a really upper game here now.
Unfortunately, we are lost.
Child leash.
That is so messed up.
They gained a damage multiplier?
I don't know if this is good for me, actually.
That may not... Actually, does that change the orbit?
No, it doesn't change the orbit.
That's good, that's good.
I was afraid they would pull in all the orbits, you know?
More damage for my children.
But it also results in more damaged children.
Holy shit!
Thank you, luck!
Wait, does that work for my planets as well?
I thought it was only like my little dude.
It feels like my planets do more damage as well.
I'm going we have here.
The hanged man, it's useless, may as well use it.
Ow.
Another hanged man?
My little follower is doing work!
Okay.
Huge.
We could potentially go step.
Potentially.
Solid.
I don't know what just happened there.
We gotta find beggars.
What is that?
I need it.
The intruder!
Invasive friend?
Spider familiar that inhibits or inhabits Isaac's face and fires quad shots of slowing tears in addition to Isaac's normal tears?
Chance for taking damage to spawn blue spiders and dislodge the intruder for the rest of the room.
While dislodged, the spider leaps at enemies, dealing contact damage and continually firing quad shots.
Okay.
So he's not dislodged yet.
When did he get dislodged here?
Chance for taking damage to spawn blue spiders and dislodge.
Okay.
Alright, well that's pretty cool.
I think very good for me.
Any followers are good.
Walking my creep nerd.
Sick.
I am pretty lost.
Nice.
Man, this book has been insane.
Wait, didn't they actually do anything just now?
I didn't get anything.
Oh, wait a minute.
I misunderstood this book.
No, I didn't.
How come I didn't get another blue heart just now?
I'm pretty nice.
My follower blocked that.
Okay, I'm glad I took that here.
Always take drugs and save environments.
The game is teaching valuable lessons.
Oh, I'm being saved so much by my guys here.
My pals are carrying this.
Okay, I lost a blue heart just now.
This room is going to be tough.
I'm going to have to rely on my friend.
Kill him, kill him.
You got it.
I need another ball of bandages.
I want to see the ultimate form.
Oh God.
My guy can't get in there.
Oh, actually not bad.
Solid.
I think I came from here.
Yeah.
What about this way?
Hey, a pill.
Nice.
That is huge.
Balls of steel.
You can't touch this.
That did a full hearted damage.
It hurts.
Okay, we gained the heart.
I saw it.
It is working.
Cheers.
Grab that.
Let's go up here.
I think I may have missed something.
Yeah, here we go.
No drops for me.
I have a feeling.
In fact, I should be having a lots of feelings this run because look at my bombs.
I can go crazy with the feelings.
Another orbital?
Dude, I'm gonna have a frickin army.
This is awesome.
I got three... what do you call it?
Mercurys right now.
Okay, so that's that here.
Let me keep looking.
Nothing.
What about here?
Here I'm having trouble knowing where to put the bomb.
It's not in here unless it's here.
Come on, man.
Oh, we haven't gone in here yet.
I didn't mean to put that bomb.
That was a mistake.
Another fly.
Wait, how come I can't see my flies?
I had three flies when I took the last pill.
I still have three flies.
I think there may be an upper limit to how many you can have.
Yeah, let me actually bomb this.
I'm so sad about that upper limit.
Like, what is that?
I finally need help, you know, and I find it and I can't get it.
There we go.
Hello.
I mean, sure, give me more money that I don't need.
Why is it always like that?
Either you're broke or you're rich, you know?
There's no in-between.
You can't be an average Joe here.
It's either limousines or the train.
This is a weird room.
I've never seen this.
Make me even richer.
Become invincible.
That is actually a pretty good one.
I like that more.
Another way to deal damage, right?
Matchstick is... nah, I'll keep the leash.
There's the boss.
Alright, my buddy.
Kill them all.
I'm just gonna sit back here and wait for you to do the work, okay?
Come on, get in there.
Thanks.
Here we go.
It's Mr. Fred.
Kill his ass.
Oh my god.
Oh, this is not gonna be a problem at all.
He got dislodged!
The spider's loose!
I need to look at him.
He's jumping around, shooting.
Nice.
Oh no, not this.
Oh, that could be good actually.
Let's see.
We got speed, that's good.
And luck.
That's a win.
That's a win right there.
Okay, now I think I move on immediately.
There's nothing else I need to do here.
Go, go, go.
The final boss, but not really.
But maybe really, in this challenge.
Oh, wait, what?
There's a bed in here now.
This is not an arcade, this is a lie.
Here, I'll give you some keys.
Oh, shit.
Whoo!
What is this?
Grant's immunity to damage from spikes and creep?
Yeah!
Wait, I fly anyway.
Fuck.
It's useless.
Ha ha!
Shit.
Nice.
We're back.
Dude, I swear to god, every time I do this, I look at my bombs and I think that's the amount of keys I have.
I get those freaking numbers mixed up.
Shit.
I'm gonna blow up this bed.
There's gotta be something with this room.
Blow this guy up, maybe?
Sure, give me more money.
How about something that can help me?
Really want to dig in here, actually.
Ah, it had to happen.
Okay, that's useless.
All right.
Random... Yay, I like that.
Yeah!
Pills have been good to me this time around.
I'm too rich.
Way too rich for my own good.
Focus, focus, focus, focus.
All the flies are my friends.
Except, are they?
Why are they... What's happening?
Oh, we are done.
Okay, we're done.
Kill them all.
Dude, I should save these flies for the boss.
I'm gonna do as much damage as I can manually.
Yeah, we're saving these.
Yield good damage.
Don't let them explode.
Oh,
maybe these do not explode, actually.
That's good.
I like it.
I want to save that black heart for the boss so we can use it to deal damage.
Okay, tomato.
Nice.
We also have an item there.
What is that?
I can't see it yet.
Something needs to die.
Oh, you.
Glaucoma.
Chance to fire concussive tears.
Maybe it'll affect my... familiars, though.
Range and fly.
I mean, okay, flies are good.
Other than that, pretty much useless pickup.
Troll bombs could be a good amount of damage.
We may need that.
Let's not forget the bombs we have also inflict poison.
So it is like a... what do you call it?
Valid damage output, you know?
Okay, here's the boss.
Are we ready?
Let's go.
I'm gonna use the tower immediately.
On the ice.
Fuck all y'all.
Yes.
Kill him, kill him.
Eyes are gone, eyes are gone!
Fuck him up, fuck him up.
This is all on you now, Bannage.
Good shit.
Oh, man, oh, man.
Okay, my guy is dislodged.
He's doing things.
It's cool.
You gotta get in there.
Gotta deal some damage.
Bombs.
Bombs?
That's right, you like that?
Enjoy.
Yes, dude!
No more solar system.
We did it.
I couldn't do it without my spider friend.
I want to give a huge thanks to my three orbitals.
Of course, the planet, shout out to you guys.
The little bleeding guy in my posse as well.
Love all of you.
The rune of something.
That was too slow.
It's okay, because I am on cloud nine.
Look at that.
It is complete, baby.
Solar system, no more.
Tastes like victory.
Okay, let's do a random run here.
Let's go.
It's Eulith.
Some more minion action today.
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
Good stuff.
I gotta get used to shooting tiles again.
I'm not used to that sort of thing.
Destroy these as well.
What a feeling.
XL.
XXL, XXL.
I feel
like I should have saved my duplication method for here.
This place is a little bit more risky.
Ah!
I got backed into a corner.
Tough, tough room.
Taking my energy.
A little haunt.
Familiar that chases and damages enemies and sometimes applies fear, eh?
Join my posse!
Oh wait, I can shoot.
Dude, I was in solar system mode.
I was waiting for my guy to damage him.
Ah, shit, that's funny.
Okay, we got the boss already in case we want to.
I want to.
No, I don't want to.
I'm gonna save one more charge.
No!
How did you hit me?
The hourglass, haven't I had that before?
Those enemies for eight sec... I mean...
It's cool, but I need this box.
I'm sorry, but the box is very much needed.
That's huge.
We take those.
Time to gurgle on my ling.
There you go.
Ah, no problem.
Chill.
We're chilling.
Wait, there's more.
The Duke of Flies.
Of men and mice.
I shall murder you until you die from it.
And that's how we do it.
Speed and damage, I take that.
I am actually not even gonna peek inside, because look at my angel right now.
33.8%.
We're going for the angel play.
That's right.
I won't even be peeking.
I will be speaking.
I apologize.
There's stones in my mouth.
Aggregates.
Ah!
I will not fall for that.
What?
Okay.
Lil Haunt is actually amazing.
I remember having this dude on my side once before, and I remember one thing very clearly.
It made me happy.
Feelings of joy.
The glass of joy was full most of the time when he was at my side.
Ah, wait.
Oh, shit.
Yeah!
Ah!
That was insanely difficult.
Thank you, Haunt.
Nate, what, what, what?
Firing for four seconds releases small fart cloud.
Cloud, why is that a question mark?
I've had that before.
But I'm glad it's not an active.
I was a little afraid of that.
Take him out.
We gotta work on some more HP.
This is the first step to success.
This could be it, guys.
I need money for it.
Today, we're gonna donate to the machine as well.
Because it's been too damn long since we did it last.
Good stuff.
How am I so good?
We blow them up!
Worth.
See, we have a problem here.
I'm at one HP.
And that's not good.
Come at me, come at me.
This will save everything.
What happened?
I was hoping for something else.
We threat the needle!
Wait, how do you say, threat in past tense?
He threat the needle?
He threw, he thrown, he...
I don't, threat?
I don't know.
Shit!
I'm in deep trouble!
Never mind, I'm good.
Okay, now we need an HP up.
And we need it now.
Mega Man, we're gonna duplicate, of course.
He's about to do lasers, yep.
No problem, no problem.
Oh man, no HP, just this bullshit.
Ah man, this is actually a horrible start.
This is a horrible start.
We have to work our way up from this pit of despair.
I'm way down there.
And I can't breathe.
Brain freeze, brain freeze!
Ah, I'm okay.
Everything was a blur, like for the past ten seconds.
I'm cornered!
I hate being cornered!
Get up here.
Okay, we need double air!
Dude, it duplicates my haunts as well.
That's huge!
I thought it was only for the guys shooting.
Okay, Lil Haunt has become super valuable now.
Oh no.
We exit!
We don't rerun.
I press space bar, not enter.
But I guess it's fine.
Eve.
That's... the horror.
Okay.
Ah, we speedrun!
Damage me!
Ah, next room we're gonna get damaged.
Damage me.
There we go, speedrun activated.
All or nothing.
Maximum speed.
We got insane damage.
We got insane skills.
What the?
Okay.
Thanks.
Low on HP here.
This is not good.
How much trouble?
Oh.
That was close.
Saved by the balls.
Faster, faster, faster.
We're speedrunning.
I don't need Noah Zazel to speedrun.
Cursed eye.
Let me think.
You know what?
Why not?
Let's try it.
It seems crazy.
I'm all in for that.
Let's try it.
It's gonna be good.
It's a little tough to hit.
I shall admit it.
Oh, wait a minute.
Taking damage teleports me.
That's...
I would say that's on the questionable side of things.
Damage is good, though.
I will say that.
Let's go.
Gimme me.
I just realized they form a heart.
That's kind of cute.
All right, come on.
Catch your breath.
Come on, little piece of shit.
Oh, God.
Nice.
This item is horrible.
Like, it is just not appreciated at all right now.
So I'm gonna go ahead and need to speedrun.
Yep.
We keep speedrunning.
Don't question it.
Just go.
100% demon mode.
Nice.
Fast to charge speed for me.
Jira?
Let's save it for something good.
Dude, my damage is immaculate.
Whatever.
I'm fine with that.
Boy.
Oh!
Oh, oh, shit!
Well, here we go.
Here we go.
I signed up for this.
I can't be crying about it.
Come here.
Not bad.
Oh, that's huge.
We get health, baby.
Health for me.
We're not taking the demon.
Nuh-uh.
Nope.
Wait, I spot a treasure room.
I want that.
I know we're speedrunning, but we can definitely make it to the treasure room.
We've been going quite fast.
We have time for it.
Oh, you almost walked into that.
I'm gonna blow it up.
Flies?
Wait, I may have fucked up here.
Wait, I have a genius plan.
Yep!
Genius plan acquired.
No, it needs a key!
It's okay, though.
Wait, we healed up as well.
That was unintentional.
Yeah, my damage is lacking.
Oh, I was hoping for a key.
Let's find a key.
A quick one.
We can do it.
We can make it.
Oh, wait, I've been here.
Shit.
I could grab a key with the Mr. Me, maybe.
Fine!
I got it.
We're Ludovicoing!
Moving on.
Okay, we take this.
We have no keys.
We don't take it yet.
We take it soon.
Wait, damage is questionable!
I may not like this!
I don't...
I may hate it.
I need tears.
It's actually fantastic for this sort of room.
Then again, the other one I had with the burst is actually even better for this room.
Yeah, my damage is poop.
I need to get my HP down to one red heart.
Maybe with a donation machine.
Go faster.
We're still on a timer.
Oh, man.
It's kind of tough.
Yeah, the damage is crap right now.
Why not?
Oh, shit!
Wait!
I'm blinking right now!
Look!
As soon as I move away...
Oh, it's here.
All the time.
What does that mean?
That's not what I was aiming, but sure.
Cool.
I'll be back for that.
That's interesting.
I want my burst shot back!
I feel like this was always so good.
Suddenly, the technique is failing me right now.
Especially mobile enemies are really tough.
Wait, well, if they run into fire themselves, then, you know...
I'm going to save my Mr. Me here.
I mean, I can still chill in a corner, let's not forget.
This is the advantage of this.
Yeah, go in.
It's peep!
I can focus on dodging while my...
You know, this is actually so convenient.
I don't have to think.
Just a little bit.
Oh, man.
I don't like it when he keeps jumping.
I may actually die here.
If I stay at max range, maybe he can't jump at me or something.
That's almost what that felt like.
Tears and shots, I mean, I'll take anything damage-related.
That makes me happy.
Let's go Mr. Me this item over here.
I guess I could also duplicate in here.
Actually, yeah.
Why not?
Yeah!
Nice.
Ex-lax, what is that again?
Sponsor puddle of slippery creep rides.
I don't like that, actually.
I think I just move on.
I know there's a blue heart there, but it's like a half blue heart and we're on a timer.
Move on.
We're actually behind the timer.
We gotta hustle.
Hustle, hustle, hustle.
Faster, faster, faster.
What do I do?
Oh, kill him!
Whoo!
Horror story.
Okay.
Faster, faster!
You gotta be kidding me.
Stay at range, just chill.
Did I get an item?
Or...
I don't know what happened.
Okay, moving on.
Oh, shit.
I am in deep trouble here.
Yeah.
Fuck me.
Randomize.
I knew I was gonna die as soon as I entered that room and I saw all those slugs.
Ha ha ha!
Speed run!
Let's fucking go.
Gloves are coming off.
No more kit gloves.
I'm gonna manhandle these fools.
Time is on my side.
There you are, hiding from me.
Fear me.
Good, move.
We look for treasure room, we move on.
Tinted rock, we blow that up.
In fact, I'm gonna do the boss immediately.
Wait, do this first.
Famine.
Wow, he stopped right in front of me.
He's kinda lucky.
And good night to you.
Gotta lick him all.
Oi!
Wait, that means we have to destroy these.
I gotta find my treasure room, though.
Like, that's a must.
What's that one?
Range.
Yeah!
Even better.
Range is huge on Azazel.
Oh, you gotta die, man.
I need bombs.
Uh...
Is that the one that destroys fucking rocks?
I'm pretty sure it is.
Wait, let me double check.
Yeah, it is, it is.
Come on, fast, we don't have time for this!
There we go.
Go, go, go!
We move.
Uh, I take this.
I can destroy things on the way, I guess.
If I get lucky with a shot.
Go, go, go!
We're gonna do the 15 bosses.
Uh, I could go in there.
What do I want to?
I don't know.
Ah, we don't have time.
Huge, this way.
Got it.
And he took the rocks?
No, not that I can see.
Oh, shit.
Ah, my charge is a little too slow.
He's messing with me.
Fuck!
That's a good one, though.
More damage.
It may not work on my laser, though, now that I think about it.
I guess I'll try and pay attention.
Kimi!
Nice.
Man, we are blazing through this.
No charging?
Alright, we gotta kill the little dudes, they're annoying.
What do we have here?
Mom's coin purse.
Sure.
Good.
Bad.
Man.
Not sure.
Ocular Rift, the Pact.
Now, that is what I'm talking about.
I'll take the Pact, thank you very much.
I make a Pact with the Devil.
Ahead of the timer, to be expected, though.
Ah, it opened for mysterious reasons.
Oi!
Ah, shit.
Thank you, Shurn.
I said, thank you, Shurn.
That is horrible.
Great use of key there.
No, this is itchy.
Thanks.
I'm not going in there.
I think bosses to the west.
Is that a little brimstone?
Hahaha.
Why not?
Twice the fun, right?
Good stuff.
Don't ever talk to me or my little friend ever again.
That's a rock.
Huge.
Massive.
We got the money as well.
Steam sale or...
restock.
Upon purchasing a shop, item a new item immediately takes place.
Hmm.
I think it may be better for this.
Here we go!
No problem.
Last eye, damage and luck.
Let's see what we got here.
Money equals power.
Sulphur.
That's for one room.
Permanently removes one HP to grant three soul hearts.
That's useless for me.
This could be good.
It's three blue hearts though.
Sulphur is actually kind of sick.
And it takes me to two out of three on Leviathan.
I forgot what it does though.
If I even know.
That's a small dam.
Hmm.
I'm taking this.
I'm banking on finding more money.
No pun intended.
I can't see my HP but I know what it is.
Hehehe.
Yeah.
How did I get hit by that?
God damn it.
Boy.
Come on, little brimstone.
That's how you sound when you die.
You sound stupid.
I'm going to murder you for that.
Oh!
No!
I tell you, nice guys finish last.
Every time.
It sucks ass.
What?
Camo on this?
Upon entering each room, Isaac comes to camouflage.
Attack him with the camouflage.
Okay, okay, okay.
Camouflage does not prevent bosses from attacking.
I like it.
You cannot see me.
I take that.
Wait.
Did that say homing?
Plus three damages.
I'm actually going to use this in here.
And then I'm going to switch over to the other one.
No problem.
Move on.
Not bad.
We're way ahead of the timer.
We're killing it.
How did that hit me, huh?
I object, your honor.
I was nowhere near that person.
My hands were in my pockets.
Come on.
We don't have time for this!
Actually, we have plenty of time.
That golden boy!
Or is it P?
It's probably P, isn't it?
Oh, gosh.
Okay, okay.
It's not that bad.
I got eight coins.
What the hell was that just now?
Something just transformed.
Member of card, we like that.
Is there anything good for sale?
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, it's the camouflage!
I see.
That's what's happening.
False PhD is black card.
Twenty-two coins, though.
That's steep.
I'll be back.
I got to find more HP.
I really did a bummer.
Or a, what do you call it?
I was floundering a little bit.
That's not the right word, either.
Curse of the tower.
I'm actually going to go ahead and say no to that.
That's right.
I refuse this gift from the gods.
We can keep it.
Shit!
What is that?
Whoa!
What?
Sick?
Just like that, huh?
I mean, we are pretty slow now.
That's kind of bad.
It's not that bad.
Thanks.
Okay, let's see.
It doesn't do anything.
Oh, God.
Kill him!
Oh, yeah, I can destroy everything.
Wait, there's a guy up here.
I need some more speed, though.
This is horribly slow.
That's a new one, Perth roll?
Three rolls, all item pedestals.
Whoa!
Okay.
Oh, my goodness.
And we even have this.
I'm taking it now because I can't find my way back here later.
We have the curse of the, I don't know where I am.
It's a problem.
Okay, at least the eternal heart is on the red one, so I'm not going to lose it immediately.
Silver lining.
Puberty!
Row those hairs.
I don't give you anything.
But I will blow you up in a second.
Oh, shit.
Oh, man, that's unfair.
That is just unfair.
Jim!
Don't do it!
I knew it was going to be a laser!
Ah.
Oh, no.
We may lose the eternal heart.
This guy is tough, right?
We got to keep moving, actually.
This is the trick.
That way he can't hit us with that.
Oh, he's dead.
Oh.
Well, there we go.
Tear's up.
I like it.
We go in here.
Oh, sick!
Blackheart's for me!
Sacrificial altar.
Yo, that could be huge!
I sacrifice all my shit.
I don't like these guys, anyway.
I like it.
Dark bomb.
Consumes redheart pickups and drops.
Yes.
Uh, grants a thundering, a harbinger familiar that spawns.
Uh, yep.
I mean, I take it, right?
There's no reason not to take that.
Moving on.
I like those.
Good.
Good, good, good.
Ooh.
We're rich!
Now we need a shop.
And then we're cooking.
Especially because there's also the back rooms, right?
We got the back rooms.
I should be walking through the poop every time.
Die!
I don't like that.
I'm a huge non-fan.
Wait, what?
What is this?
Oh, there's one there.
Fuck!
I think my... what do you call it?
Acetyr has just messed me up there.
By blowing up the run.
You're dead, son.
That was a pleasant room.
Tech X replaces tears with charged laser rings!
YEAH!
Now we're cooking!
Why is it always on Azazel?
Oh, that's lovely, that's lovely that.
Well, we can't be stopped now.
In fact, we still gotta hurry.
I don't know how far ahead of the timer we are, but we are ahead of the timer, I'm pretty sure.
Keep moving, keep moving.
Somehow I went to every place but the boss room.
It's actually kind of unbelievable.
Good night.
I don't like you.
Are we done?
We're not done.
This way, this way.
Oh, a shot.
Oh, here we go, here we go.
Uh, uh, I go down.
Woke up a Lyle.
That's good.
Panic button is whatever.
Oh, I could also Perth row this one.
I take that and I Perth row.
Excuse me.
I don't understand.
Why didn't it work?
Fuck!
I misunderstood.
I'm upset.
Give me judgment.
Death.
Uh, die, you die.
This guy dies.
We don't have time.
Give me, move.
Actually insane.
Wait, uh, uh, uh, here.
I need to destroy all these rocks.
The sound is too satisfying.
I need to do it.
Oh, that feels good.
Mom, I got presents for you.
Enjoy.
Yeah, you like that?
You like that?
Uh, kill this guy.
These guys.
There we go.
Polaroid.
Uh, we're going in.
Wish me luck, ladies and gentlemen.
Let's see what we got here.
Uh, cursed eye, charged shot.
Oh, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, hold up.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Little haunt.
Yeah.
But is there more?
There's not more.
That sucks.
Oh, I thought you were transparent.
Opacity at zero.
Instead it was like 80.
Okay, this music is so good.
I'm going to lock in here.
Stay on his side, actually.
Never mind, he does that.
I had no idea he did that.
That's a new one.
He's never done that before.
Oh yeah, he's eating the hearts.
Sick.
Health up, baby.
Damage.
I'm somehow not hitting anything.
Blow him a mind.
Give me that heart.
I know the guy could consume it, you know, but this is a definite healing.
The next one he's going to take and he's going to maybe give me black hearts.
I hope so.
Okay, we got to chill down a little bit here.
Eternal heart?
I think I'll save that.
Try not to pick it up.
Oh, that's my friend.
Pick it up, pick it up.
Show me what's good.
A pill.
I'll take a puberty.
What's happening here?
Where are you?
There you are.
Dude, how the... I'm too slow.
I can't outrun the bombs.
It's actually kind of not good for me.
Okay, that's good.
That's huge.
Just keep shooting him.
Just keep shooting.
Nice.
I keep getting more damage, by the way, from the book.
How does that actually work?
Can I just keep doing it?
Can you damage it for the current room?
I just keep doing it.
Keep giving me damage.
Oh, shit, you came out of nowhere.
Yeah, you spawn there.
They're jumping, they're jumping.
Oh, what is that now?
Oh, it's you.
My little haunt is helping.
Quite a bit.
Okay, pick this one up, dark bomb.
Come here.
Are you gonna give me something good?
A card?
Okay.
What's that gonna be, though?
The tower.
Why not?
Let's do it.
Seems like fun.
Nice.
Oh, there's another black card here.
I missed it.
He just consumed the red heart without giving anything in return.
Angel time.
Yeah, give me that.
Take that bomb, take it.
Another one for your bomb.
Get over here.
Show me what you got.
He didn't give nothing in return.
Classic.
Come on.
Oh, we're done.
Well, there we go.
Thank you.
Uh, so now we got this.
Parasitoid.
You have to fire egg sacs here to spawn a blue spider.
Also slow enemies and spawn a small pool of slowing creep.
Okay, we still gotta hurry, though.
I'm taking this.
And then I'm just gonna check here if we missed anything.
We did not.
Okay.
Go, go, go.
Okay, we still gotta hurry here.
Oh, items.
MC.
Ah, wait, go this way.
That was bad.
What the?
Oh, hey, a lot of money.
Look at that.
No way.
Is that a Bible?
Book of Revelations.
I mean, I think I want that.
Fuck the damage.
I take this.
We got tomatoes inbound.
Bogeys at six o'clock.
Oh, not the eyes.
Don't these eyes look like those emojis with the red mouth and then the eyes on the side?
Just a little bit.
What's up here?
Nice.
Oh, that's not a bomb I can pick up.
Peace.
The Hank man is useless.
Where do we go?
Let's go bottom right.
I cannot believe that just happened.
Dude, I'm actually unstoppable.
My items are too good.
So many troll bombs?
Oh, I didn't mean to remove my camouflage.
Fight room.
We may not have time for that.
Go this way.
It should be here, right?
Like, where is this boss?
Hello?
Oh,
light safe.
Conserve HP.
Ah, you're kidding me.
That didn't just happen.
Insane.
Hey, buddy.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Conquest.
Well, this is going to be a very short quest for you.
Not a lot of pros, only cons.
Where are you?
There we go.
This one.
What was that one again?
Dash across the screen.
I mean, no, thanks.
I'll keep this.
Thank you very much.
And no devil deals?
That's too bad.
Okay.
I say north.
I feel like I'm cursed with the troll bombs in this run.
I don't know what I just took damage from.
Thanks.
We almost have enough for another soul heart.
Actually, I should just be sitting back and playing safe.
There's no reason to go all crazy.
I have insane damage and range.
It is almost like a brimstone.
Not quite, but, you know, almost.
Oh, yeah.
Satisfying.
We have the sun as well.
I mean, this can't go wrong.
Dude, look at how fast I'm charging my circle now.
I barely need to, like, I can almost spam it, you know?
It's kind of crazy.
Get an extra soul heart.
It lives.
Not for long.
Trust me on that one.
Prepare for the eyes of north.
Easy peasy lemon squeezy.
Holy shit, the damage is insane, dude.
The damage is wild.
Okay, so hold on.
We got, oh, we got three options.
I'm gonna go in here first.
Dude, what the fuck?
Okay, give me something good at least.
Hit a frampus, fires a brimstone, laser tag, and oh, no, I don't like that.
That sucks.
Wait, where did the thing go?
I can't answer anymore.
What the fuck?
Okay, we're going up.
Time for heaven.
Cathedral.
It's time for Isaac to taste my breath.
I could have sworn last time I went inside there first and it still worked.
Maybe it didn't.
No problem at all.
Honestly, Isaac's gonna be a walkover.
In fact, I call it now.
I'm not even gonna lose one point of HP in that fight.
And you can take that to the bank.
Actually, the 54 coins I have have been helping me immensely here.
Money equals power.
I go this way.
Appear.
What a room.
I'm glad I have crazy items.
Every time this song is on, I keep thinking he's saying expect- and he's about to say expectation, but then he stops short and I'm always disappointed.
He's playing with my expectations.
What's that?
Daggers.
Wait, what is that one?
Removes curses and grants once.
I mean...
I didn't look.
Did that actually give me a soul heart even though I didn't remove a curse?
I'm not sure.
I fucked it up.
I had one job.
Let's check out this room.
No.
Hey!
Not bad.
Yes.
Okay, fuck this.
We gotta hurry.
I gotta see what happens if we keep hurrying here.
The tower.
Eowas.
Oh, Eowas.
That should work on pretty much anything.
Okay.
Wasting a bit of time here.
Okay, that's useless.
So what's happening in here?
Oh, god.
Grant me, sucker.
What was that?
Oh, I think I may like range more.
Actually, wait, wait.
Actually, hold on.
Plus tiers?
We could maybe turn into a machine gun with that.
Ah, I mean, come on.
We gotta do that.
That is amazing.
Holy shit.
I'm excited.
Yeah,
well, the range is definitely a problem, but not a big one.
God damn it.
I forget I have this.
Let me... I don't know where there's a good indicator.
There's none in here.
Maybe there.
Yeah.
Quick, quick, quick.
Money and a chest?
That's very underwhelming.
Boss is here.
I think we do it.
Go for it.
No damage run now.
I'm not gonna take any damage against this fool.
You're dead, son.
Flawless.
What was that sound?
Oh, yeah, we're doing this.
Fuck, yeah.
I forgot about this.
Wait, can I... can I go in that door?
Eight-inch nails?
It replaces tiers with nails that... yes?
Uh, wait.
I guess it doesn't matter for me.
Charm of the vampire?
Heels... uh, sure.
I take it all.
Short of glass?
Can't just spawn a red heart when damage... blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Cool.
Why not?
Give it.
I can't get it.
Get in here, it seems.
Unfortunately.
My damage is very good.
Teleport me.
No problem.
What's that?
Sacrificial dagger?
Sure.
Let me take that.
I just realized charging up is kind of useless with the, uh, with the camouflage thing we have on this character.
Because it gets broken every time I try to charge, you know?
Convert it.
A spider?
What the hell is that, my friend?
Didn't even convert for me.
Convert, convert, convert, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Do it.
Question mark!
I've had it with your shit.
You hear me?
I don't know who you are, but you're not me.
You're something else.
Where are you?
Oh, wait, I'm shooting things.
I mean, I, my character's just broken at this point.
This, huh?
What?
I don't understand what just happened.
How did I get here?
I think I fell down into something.
Oh, shit.
Mom, what is this place?
You got a lot of hands on you.
Mom, why are your hands so big?
New music.
This is so good.
I can't believe it.
It's look, oh, wait a minute.
It's like a mix of all the other levels.
I see what's happening.
Okay, I'm actually going to take my time.
I'm not going to speedrun anymore.
Although that may have been the result of speedrunning a little bit.
What the fuck is that?
Look at this place.
Oh, that hurts.
Okay, got it.
Eve's bird foot.
No, let me have cancer.
I mean, this is crazy.
You know what?
Why not?
Full gamble.
Come on.
Actually, I don't need anything from this machine.
Fuck it.
I have everything in the world.
Like, what could I possibly want from that?
Boss is here.
Kind of what I explore, though.
I need to explore this place.
How was that sound just now?
Did my follower just eat something?
God, I love that.
This is so good.
Shot speed up.
Nice.
What's that?
Hey, that could come in handy.
Maybe.
Let's do this.
Not that it matters, I guess.
Uh, where's the other pill?
Where's the pill I just had?
Oh, there it is.
Wait, is there a pill?
There's multiple bosses?
Look at the freaking map.
What the hell?
I'm taking damage from something.
What's happening?
I don't understand what's going on.
Delirium.
Oh, I'm gonna rock your world.
You don't know who you're up against, sir.
It's Isaac.
The one and only.
I don't even know what I'm shooting at.
I'm just shooting.
Hoping I'm hitting something.
Oh, are you down here?
You're down there.
Got it.
You're a worm.
I'm taking damage from something and I don't know what it is.
There's something on top of me.
Wait, he's turning.
Oh, he's morphing into different bosses.
I just keep taking damage somehow.
I don't know how.
I'm not getting hit by anything.
That was that's bad for me.
You like bombs?
I need to focus here.
Dude, this guy has HP.
Wow.
I don't know how I'm taking damage.
I don't understand.
What am I getting hit by?
I think my followers are damaging me.
It's a freaking coup d'etat.
Mutiny.
Okay, that was on me.
That was on me.
The bomb just stole my heart.
You fucker, it was my heart.
I was gonna heal and you stole it.
Man, that was cool though.
I don't know what the hell was going on in that run, but I liked it.
Jesus.
Delirium.
That's how I feel right now.
I feel delirious.
Uh, I think it's time we do a greed run.
Just to change things up a little bit, because that was kind of crazy.
But before we do, quick break, and then I'm gonna go get some more drinks.
So I'll see you in a bit.
It was close.
Lazarus.
Lazarus, it is.
I like it.
Let's go this way.
Magic scale.
Oh, nice.
What a start.
Wow.
Does it get better?
I don't think it does.
No bombs though.
Here we go.
I've never done this as Lazarus.
In fact, I haven't done this as many characters, but I'm not used to not being as Hazel in this mode.
It's fine though.
Lazarus is all around just solid, I feel like.
He's good.
Could turn out well, you know?
You never know.
Things can go from zero to crazy real fast.
Okay, it's starting to get a little crazy in here.
We gotta thin these numbers.
Fuck.
Focus.
Oh no.
Oh, I got...
dude, I couldn't move.
Whoa.
Jesus Christ.
I'm fighting for my life here, and it's the first wave.
I don't know why it's so hard.
Okay.
Well, I need some upgrades.
That's half price.
Increase size, speed, and a random pill.
Cube of meat.
I don't like any of this.
I could re-roll.
Shit.
I think I'm gonna take this.
Yeah!
Huge.
Dude, every time I get a new item there, it's always discounted.
That is kind of massive.
I need a key.
I'll be back for this underwear.
I need it.
Tammy's head.
I mean, that's fine.
Not that exciting.
Having that extra speed though is gonna help a lot.
Actually, the fact that it's like one charge could be pretty good.
Hopefully it charges faster than...
like, hopefully multiple times per wave here.
Otherwise, it's really bad.
God, I have no damage.
This is just painful.
Okay, so it did recharge there.
We killed this guy first.
Web stock!
Fuck!
I did not see that rock at all.
I gotta focus.
It's just this guy now.
Come on.
Get away from him.
Yeah, there we go.
Nine coins.
We can get the underwear.
Range and flies.
I mean...
Oh, I want that so much too.
Should I...
Wait.
We're gonna get a bit more money though, right?
If I do this.
I could also consider dying and get damage up, right?
It's not a bad idea, actually.
I could walk into that curse room.
Oh, shit.
Dude, the jumping frequencies off the charts.
He's gonna keep jumping.
Oh, my God.
There's no way.
There's no fucking way.
Okay, thank God.
Kill these things.
Whoo, that was close.
Ah.
Yes.
No.
Hmm, but then again.
Yes.
Kill me.
Nice.
Now we... Oh, wait.
I don't have a bomb?
I miscalculated this.
Well, I guess I didn't expect there to be a chest I couldn't open.
Fuck.
No.
I kind of just want to restart.
This is horrible.
God damn.
Okay, we go down here.
Okay, thank God.
A bit of healing is much needed.
Or just some extra HP.
I mean, not really healing, but you know.
This may be worth it, actually, to buy.
Nothing else is on sale, so...
We gotta start.
Ah, come on.
I kind of like the bomb spawn.
That's fine.
Nah, bro.
Not bad.
I feel like my damage suddenly got a lot better.
There we go.
I'll take this.
18 coins.
That's surely something we can work with.
Pentagram?
It's actually not a bad idea.
I like it.
Oh man, is that the good mushroom?
I need that.
We gotta save up for it.
14 coins should be doable, right?
Yeah, this is good.
This is good.
Good damage.
Good speed.
I think we're cooking.
Oi, yo, yo.
No problem.
10 coins.
Okay, we're working our way up.
Also, I need a key.
Oh man, this is...
Oh, this is rough.
My tiny size is having an advantage.
One down.
Clean so far.
Oh god.
Uh, I don't know if I should do it.
Do I sell my soul to the devil?
Oh shit.
Okay, I would know why the fire hit me.
Piece of shit fire.
Take it out.
What are you doing?
Oh, right.
That was close.
There we go, baby.
What's that?
Head of Krampus?
Uh, yeah, why not?
From one head to the next.
I'll take it.
And we need four more coins.
I think I gotta buy the key, though.
This is where we're at.
Or I go in here and hope for the best.
I can still die one time, right?
But then I lose an HP, so is it worth?
I don't know.
We take this.
Big chubby.
That's not even that good, in my opinion.
Okay, that's big.
The healing is massive.
Okay, since we got an extra heart, we're doing this.
Two keys!
Yo, I should have got in here.
Man, cannot believe that.
Heal.
Uh, right.
Let's go.
I think we're good on this floor.
Cheers.
The dank depths are calling me.
We got the photo.
That's cool.
I can go in here.
That's even more cool.
Ah, that's boring.
Little brimstone is very meh, in my opinion.
The keys for sale this time.
I didn't mean to do that!
But I guess I have a bomb now.
It is what it is.
Wait, I can barely see where my character is.
He's too tiny.
My menus are bigger than me.
It's very confusing.
Yeah.
Damage is getting a lot better than the start, for sure, though.
I'm no longer falling behind here.
I have to use so much RAM to figure out where I am on the screen.
Oh, they gotta explode, right?
No, okay.
They're not.
We done?
Okay.
24 coins.
I think more HP is what the doctor ordered.
Odd mushroom.
Oh, that's really good.
Fuck me, I need that.
More money for me.
Oh, this guy needs to die, I guess.
Oh, that's my friend.
No problem.
17 coins?
Yes, we take this.
We also have to remember to save up some coins for the end, right?
This is the big deal.
We got some healing, so we can...
Wait, what is this?
Oh!
The wooden cross!
We fall asleep?
Huh?
Did we just heal?
I think we just healed.
Oh, that's cool.
Ha!
So if you have a bed, you can go in and heal.
I wonder if you can keep doing it.
Immediately, my mind is going to stepping.
You know, the stepping possibilities.
But I guess that never happened before, but maybe I was full HP.
I guess that could be the case.
Good night.
Demons!
We can take a peek.
Okay, I mean, I think I'm going to take that one.
I believe in my dodging capabilities.
I believe I can do it.
Gotta believe in me.
Let's go.
Halfway through.
I think on the next floor, we're going to start saving.
That depends how confident we are, I guess.
Nice!
That's two out of three on mushrooms.
We buy a third mushroom.
Spider mod!
I don't like that too much.
What's on sale?
Nothing is on sale.
What?
I could also re-roll, I guess.
I guess spider mod is not super important.
Not for this game mode, I don't think.
Keys five dollarinos.
Got a couple dollars here.
I'm going to go in here, I think.
No, I'm going to lose my black hearts.
How am I not getting hit?
My little size must be doing wonders here.
The way I'm keeping track of all my characters is where my projectiles are.
I can't...
Dude, I have so much trouble seeing where my character is.
I need an accessibility option for that.
I feel like that should be made clearer in the game, like where your guy is.
Open up.
21 coins.
You know what?
I take that.
I re-roll.
Wait, am I going to waste this now?
Hold on.
Next up is boss.
We're not... are we going to get money for that?
I don't remember.
Lost contact.
Teals collide with and destroy enemies.
I mean, that's good.
We like that.
A bit of extra protection.
Uh, I'm going to try this.
Oh, money, money, nice.
Okay, so we do get money.
Come here.
Dude, this guy is so tough to hit.
I don't understand.
Okay, he died, he died.
He's healing.
Okay, okay, 23.
Uh, we can re-roll.
BFF.
Doubles the damage of familiars and...
Double the brimstone, huh?
That could be kind of sick.
But this one is also not bad.
Wait, what does my other familiar do?
Uh, is it that one?
Charge is slowly in the direction.
Yeah, that's not interesting.
I think I'm going to go for this one.
The familiars are not going to be what's going to win me this.
I don't think.
I have good damage, though.
It's respectable.
More devil shenanigans.
What the hell?
Oh, dude, I got to try that.
That looks so freaking cool.
What is that?
A baton.
Evil plus damage up.
Oh my god, hold on.
Speed damage replaces all heart containers with black hearts.
Whoa!
Chance to fire fear tears increases with luck.
Well, we have good luck.
This sounds really dope.
Wait, does that mean the hearts in the shop are black as well?
Oh!
Boo!
Liar.
Hands on fire.
All heart containers?
Nah, bro.
That's a lie.
That's not what all means.
Bastards.
Okay.
It's okay, though.
No red hearts.
It's just another day at the office.
We can do this.
Tarot cloth.
That was the effects of most cards.
I don't care.
Let's see if we can get some nice stuff from these fires.
Hey, the bow!
Why is it not black?
Bro, what?
Am I misreading this?
Replaces all heart containers with black hearts.
I don't get it.
I don't know.
I guess this is not a heart container.
What the fuck is a heart container, then?
Is it the place out back behind the shop where they throw out all the hearts, or what?
I don't get it.
box okay nice spawns a blue attack fly yeah I think I want that instead of the mushroom removes curses and grants one so let me see the grants a soul heart without curses it does okay fantastic now this over here I'm actually gonna get in
Aewas.
Right here, baby.
That's an Aewas spot, if I ever saw one.
What is that?
Power of Waves.
Poseidon.
Oh yeah, right.
My tears are blocking.
Aquarius leaves a trail of creep that deals a lot of damage and copies tear effects.
Nice!
That means they're gonna be feared if they follow my tears.
Or my creep, I mean.
Little Steven.
Well, we're making a whole army here, and I like it.
I do.
I'm gonna go in here.
Okay.
May not have been worth it.
It's a gamble.
Oh, Jesus, dear lord.
I got lasers too.
Dude, I cannot see where my character is.
Not only is he tiny, he's the exact same color as the level.
Nice.
Faster, faster, faster.
Beautiful.
Man, this guy has a lot of HP.
Oh, it's the Sippermen.
I have the perfect one-liner when I kill him.
Dude, I'm so friggin' fast.
1.75 speed.
The other guy's just chilling for some reason.
I don't know what's up with him.
Oh, he's just waiting.
Yeah, that's right!
Sip it, bitch!
Okay, so do we save food?
I mean, do we save money?
I think we save.
At this point, we save.
We save it.
Full save mode.
Everything gets saved.
I didn't mean to step on that.
That was a mistake.
God damn it.
I gotta stay mobile.
Okay.
Sick.
35 coins.
I think we move on.
Wait, there's just a normal hatch here.
Isn't that weird?
That's hella weird, man.
Oh, that's cheap.
Ah, we gotta buy that.
Ah, man, that's... yeah.
It's too cheap not to buy.
We take, like, this amount.
This is good.
I have to remember, I don't need to dodge.
My tears absorb their tears.
It's a force field.
Oh, god.
What do I take that much from?
I don't even know where I am.
Oh, I'm here.
Okay.
Fuck.
Focus, focus, focus.
Wait, is that my leech?
Dude, shit's getting out of control.
Focus.
Okay, okay.
41 coin arenas.
We go again.
Oh, my goodness.
That was a massive active.
Okay.
Where are you?
There you are.
Oh, you bastard.
Lost definitely a lot of HP on this.
Uh, wait, we can leave or we can click this button?
Why would I click that button when I can leave?
I'm confused about that.
I'll take a couple more of these.
There we go.
No more.
I click again.
I fear nothing.
Ah, that's why you want to do it.
Of course.
Oh, you're stuck, are you?
That's too bad.
Oh.
Okay, that was a bit of a fight there.
Dude, sacrificial altar is gonna go hard.
Gympie!
Drop it so hard, but yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm down for that.
Guppy's collar.
I could also take that, because I can go back and honestly, that's totally worth.
Three more of these.
I did waste a lot of money just now, though.
I did, I did, I did.
It's okay.
It's fine.
Wait, we can fly!
Why?
Leviathan.
That's it.
Okay, move on.
Cheers.
Okay, here we go.
Believe in me.
This needs to be flawless.
We're actually just a sasil now, but better.
25 coins!
No way!
Just in time!
Wow.
Oh, you're so dead, son.
Actually, I should not sell the skin before the creature has been slaughtered.
Oh, crap.
Okay, this guy has more HP than normal, I think.
This is weird.
Oh, wait, it's healing him!
I'm an idiot.
I should have looked at the coins.
We're gonna play Space Invaders.
Okay, these are healing hearts.
Shit.
I mean, it is what it is.
My output is more than his healing.
Oh my god.
That's cool.
Come on.
Wait, doors are open!
If they open again, I'm gonna go in.
That's where these guys came from.
I'm ready.
Oh, you're done.
You're done, son.
Key bomb has appeared.
Okay, donation!
Go!
Kay now holds paper something.
Paperclip?
Everything is tribunal.
What?
Well, there we go.
What a success story for Lazarus.
Oh, yeah.
Victory lap.
Victory clap.
Victory nap.
See you, guys.
I'm ready to nap, though.
Okay, move on.
I want to do... I hereby declare that I am gonna...
Wait, unlocked by beating question mark.
That could be delirium.
Let's do Bethany.
I wanted to play with Bethany.
Because she's kind of interesting.
So we have this Bible book that does things.
And we have four blue hearts right now.
Okay.
Whatever that means.
Wait.
Oh, I'm in greed mode.
I didn't mean to.
It's fine.
We do another greed.
Maybe a good opportunity to learn this character.
The fuck was that?
I don't know why that just exploded, but sure.
That's cool.
Speed and range.
Speed is good, because I'm slow AF.
It's gonna be rough going in the beginning here.
That's not that bad.
How come it's not that bad?
This is very chill for some reason.
What is that doing in?
Oh yeah, spawns a fly.
That explodes.
Get on fast.
Good.
Spawn a fly.
Not bad.
Please don't laser me.
Okay, good.
Ah, shit.
Wait,
I bet converter is amazing on Bethany.
Forgot her name there for a sec.
You can stack up blue hearts, you know, like five of them maybe, and you can't lose them, and you just convert them.
Torn photo.
Buddy in a box grants a following familiar with a randomized appearance, fire rate, damage, bonus tier effects.
Familiar traits are randomized at the start of each new floor.
I think I gotta go for the guaranteed just good upgrade here.
I'll take the torn photo.
Nothing is on sale, unfortunately.
What if we could also re-roll?
Gym.
Gym has been naughty.
You know what I could do?
I could blow this up, but I can't, because I don't have a bomb, but I could get a bomb, and then blow it up.
I am gonna gamble a little bit here.
Yes.
Yeah.
Abso-fucking-lutely.
We take that.
Oh, shit.
I thought my one was a key, but it's my blue heart.
Ah, shit.
I need more money.
I'm once again asking for donations.
I need it so I can buy the key.
Come on, Steven.
You like flies?
Steven's brother is angry.
Hey, I didn't start it.
Your brother started this.
Oh, no.
We're gonna be dealing with all of these at the same time.
That's rough.
Oh, god!
I almost got stuck.
Insane.
Actually so well done.
Uh, we could buy this.
Jumper cables?
It's probably something to do with charging and active, and I don't like that.
So I'm gonna do this.
Dead bird.
Oh, my gosh.
Bethany.
Your face.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
That's a coin.
Let's do this one.
Who do I focus first?
Probably the jumping dude.
He's the scariest.
Wait, did the snake die?
He must have died accidentally.
Angels!
Book of Revelations.
Wait, times one inner wisp?
Wait, I need to understand this.
Times one inner wisp?
So if I have one inner wisp, I get five HP.
Doesn't shoot.
Spawns a little harbinger on death for the room.
Wait, does she have like separate mechanics for every book then, or what?
I actually forgot about that.
I had some item last time that also had like an effect here.
Five coins.
I don't think I'm gonna buy anything.
Actually, maybe this heart.
Nah.
No, no, no, we don't need it.
We don't need it.
We move on.
It's that simple.
Oh, wait a minute.
I see a tinted rock.
Was there a bomb in here?
There's not even a bomb.
What the fuck?
Oh, shit.
Okay, we go.
It's fine.
Let me try and activate this.
Let's wait until we start the fight.
Just in case, you know.
Stapler.
Oh, I like that a lot.
I'm gonna buy that.
But first we go here.
Two picks.
Yes, solid.
More damage.
Let me try this now.
So wait, we have one wisp and it has like a little cross inside of it.
Oh, the wisp has five HP.
So I want the guy to die.
So he spawns the guy, right?
But I'm not gonna sacrifice.
I'm just gonna let it happen naturally.
We're chilling.
Wait, I can do another one.
Two of them.
Dude, let's go for three.
Are you excited for three?
I'm excited for three.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
All right, then.
I lost one fly.
Does that mean one of those guys spawned?
I don't see one.
Oh, yeah, he's there.
He's there.
He ain't doing shit though.
He's just sitting there.
What a useless little man.
Another one.
Focus.
Dude, I'm actually kind of cracked at this game.
I may actually be, you know, unfathomably good.
I just realized I'm taking this.
Random pills.
Yes.
That's speed.
Nice.
Whatever.
It's okay.
I would love the milk as well.
I would love the milk.
Oh, wait, look at that.
Huh?
It doesn't have a ladder, so that just leads to the next level or what?
Why would I do that?
Isn't that, like, anti-ideal here?
Like, you don't want to do that.
Oh, okay, we spawned a dude.
We spawned a dude.
That's okay.
So, I wonder if the fly works in a way where they don't have to touch the enemy to absorb the damage.
Anytime I take damage, they die first.
That's kind of crazy if that's the case.
Okay, we got money, which means we can get even more HP now.
I could buy this as seven, so...
Oh, we're not gonna have enough for the key.
Well, where did that come from?
I need it!
Dude, bomb?
There was no bomb.
We gotta re-roll.
Where's the Bob Lebowski?
Actually, are you for real?
It triggers the effect of the... Wait, what?
Hold on.
Oh, every active has some kind of interaction with my character.
It's not just books.
Holy shit.
Okay, that's kind of crazy.
Treasure rooms.
Oh, okay, that's kind of cool.
Okay, here's the plan.
We're gonna go in here.
Cursed.
Wait, where's that one again?
Oh, no, it's that one where we teleport.
Maybe it's okay.
We're not gonna take damage here.
This is the plan, at least.
Uh-oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, god.
Oh, goodness gracious.
Okay, he's dead, he's dead, he's dead.
I can shoot a bunch of shit too, just like you.
Dude, the angle shots like this is actually kind of crazy.
I wonder if my flies that I spawn or my little guys will prevent the curse from happening, you know, when I take damage.
That could be massive.
So, something opened.
Oh.
Oh, money!
Well, we got enemies!
It's just one guy.
It's okay.
No!
Okay, my fly didn't disappear.
How come I wasn't teleported?
Oh, mid-charge!
Oh, shit.
Okay, well, in that case, that is totally good.
Fuck, yeah.
Well, I'll be buying all kinds of things.
I'll take this one.
Pay to win.
What will I take then?
Speedball could be pretty good as well, but honestly, I just want to re-roll.
Then again, I'm spawn one of three.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay, maybe I just take that.
But imagine getting a bomb.
I just want a bomb.
I didn't mean to do that.
Fuck me.
Jesus juice is out of the question now.
I guess we'll commit.
You know what?
Fuck Jesus juice.
I love this.
Oh, yeah.
It was totally worth.
No bomb still, which is insane to me.
Fuck, I need to buy that key.
I'm going to leave this behind because I fucking ran into the thing.
Oh, that hurts.
That really hurts.
Yeah, you better puke.
Okay, let's see what we got down here.
Boo!
I hate that.
Come on!
Oh, you were close to getting me there.
I'm actually kind of too fast.
Three flies on me.
What does it mean?
I feel like shot speed is actually biting me in the ass here a little bit, having too much shot speed.
It's harder to, you know, have all my shots hit.
Four flies.
Wait, can I see what it does then?
I'm not sure what it does when I have four flies.
Yeah, I'm not actually understanding the system at all.
15 coins.
No bombs.
Not that I need one, probably.
I'm intrigued by this.
Okay, well, the gym was not good.
Okay, a bar of soap is interesting.
This is a very good deal right here.
I could take that and the deal.
More tears.
Wait, how fast is my tears?
It's actually pretty fast, but we can make it faster.
Ah, that's also good, but that's a good deal right there.
Save up for a key now, because we get to re-roll in that room, right?
It almost feels like I'm playing a Zazel again.
I somehow always end up with an Zazel-like character.
Careful.
What are you doing?
I need to get this guy off his horse.
I'm losing my mind.
There we go.
Good knockback on this.
Perfect play.
And I'm good.
I think I'm going here.
What is it with these runes?
No bombs to speak of.
I think I'll take a key then.
It's not that exciting.
I'm more excited about this, honestly.
There we go.
Three out of three.
What does it do?
Spun.
Okay, we developed massive, you know, thingies on our face.
Are you aware?
Maybe it means all pills are good now or something.
You know, that could be what that means.
Or something else, I'm not sure.
Oh, what?
What the fuck is that?
No!
We're shooting diagonally!
Well, I hate it.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God, dude.
Wait, what?
Now we're not shooting diagonally.
I'm confused.
This game is messing with me.
Whoa.
Oh, there's little hearts.
They're tiny.
Oh, shit.
No.
Coffee?
Ipikak.
40 damage?
Say what?
Replaces tears with an arcing explosive poison shot.
Self-damage?
Oh, God.
I'm scared.
Oh, okay.
I see.
Huh.
Holy shit.
All right.
I need pyromaniac.
Damage is good.
It's very good.
Angels.
Holy candle?
Pachal candle, keep the flame burning.
Familia that grants a stacking tears bonus for each room cleared without taking damage up to a maximum of plus two.
Taking damage extinguishes its flame and resets the bonus.
That's such a cool idea for an item.
Can I do it?
I lost it all.
Also, I just misremembered.
Of course, it's giving me the... It's not healing me.
It's doing the other thing.
There's no more money to be had here.
We're done pretty much.
So, I think I'm just gonna buy one of these.
Two of them.
Yeah.
Get some HP going.
Oh.
You want something?
Nice.
Let's try and keep the candle burning.
Okay.
This way.
Oh, I'm not gonna re-roll that.
That is massive, that.
Oh, not bad at all.
Oh, guys.
It's time.
It's time for that.
We need to save up.
I need it.
It is so good.
That's for you.
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay.
Calm down.
Fuck.
I thought I just... I don't know what I thought.
Dude, this damage is crazy.
Wow.
I don't even need to charge it.
I kill.
I blast.
Wait, what?
Oh, right.
Wait, these are bombs.
Oh, shit.
That count as bombs.
Right, of course.
Obviously.
Uh, well, uh... Hold on.
We're gonna be looking for secret rooms.
Huh?
Oh, there we go.
Ah, okay.
Okay, got it.
Okay, that's not gonna open there.
Forlet tusk group boop.
Fortune cook.
What?
Rarey damage.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Times one middle wisp.
Two HP, three damage.
Tears have a chance to transform enemies into random wisps.
Whoa, okay.
I like it.
What did I have before?
Why can't I pick this up?
This item right here is farting.
What if I re-roll now?
No way.
D4.
Perilous item.
No, re-rolls each item currently held into a different item from the same pool.
Whoa.
I don't know if I want that.
That sounds questionable.
I'll head in here.
Replaces tears with... But wait, how does that work with my...
I guess we'll find out.
Oh, there's just nails in the air.
Got it.
Why did I even think?
Of course, it's just gonna be nails in the air.
I'm digging it.
Oh, shit.
They came from the top.
Well, they got me there.
We need to develop a new strategy here.
This is not working.
We're gonna stand over here and just shoot in every corner like this.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Wait, we didn't get any money from that?
Maybe I already picked it up.
Probably.
No!
Wait.
Oh, yeah!
Error!
Mimics the effect of a random... Yes?
Gigante Bean.
The size of Isaac's force is in... I mean...
I don't want more range, honestly.
Yeah, fuck that.
Not a fan.
I'd rather re-roll things.
Fuck!
I'm scared!
That's for you!
Oh, God.
Not bad, not bad at all!
I'm not sure what's happening in this game.
I'm confused.
Again.
What if I give you something now?
Hehehehehe.
Tears down.
No.
Well, that was not good.
Wait, my familiar shooting bombs as well.
That's fucking crazy.
Oh, my God!
The damage!
Hey, you like this, sir?
Oh, you did, son!
A lump of coal, why not?
I do take that.
Wait, I should be able to find secrets like this, no?
But we already found the secret room, I guess.
Didn't we?
We did.
Nice.
Moving on, baby!
Sheol!
No, she not.
Sheong!
No secrets.
No!
I will not.
Nice!
Rot my meat!
I love it.
Hi-yo!
It's okay, it's okay.
It's not okay, I'm damage- I'm just damaging my kill.
Kill.
My kill.
Focus.
Kill it!
Nice.
Don't get teleported!
You come in, you come in!
The timing was unfortunate, but we got to the secret, so we're good.
Thanks.
I just saved that from happening.
Two and a half.
Nice!
Ansys!
Let me see everything.
I don't need to see nothing, I guess.
Uh, I kind of need some healing here.
I'm going to buy this.
Yeah, we got to play this safe, because shit's kind of dangerous right now.
What's that?
Two of hearts?
Item multiplier?
Oh, doubles Isaac's red hearts.
Oh, that's actually kind of dope.
That's going to come in handy.
Jesus Christ.
Where are you?
There's someone else in here.
Okay.
Oh my god, dude.
What the fuck?
Holy shit.
I have pretty good damage.
I just want to say that.
Okay, I need a key now.
No more messing around.
It's a sack of pennies.
I don't like that at all, actually.
I re-rolled those.
Uh-huh.
Bombs explode in a large cross shape.
We do it.
Let me see if it works with this.
It doesn't.
Why doesn't that work?
Maybe it's not technically a bomb.
Let's look for secrets.
We found it already.
Time to bomb the shit out of these guys.
Yeah, you ain't nothing.
That was on me.
I did it.
I was mine.
Pop up.
Show your face.
I will murder your ass.
What the shit?
I don't know what's happening right now, but I love it.
Man, my bombs are sort of just going.
It's kind of scary.
I feel like this item is just as dangerous as it is.
Uh, I'm just going to heal up here, because why not?
Angel time.
Tears and soul hearts adds copies of the Bible.
I like it.
I do.
Hey, you know what?
Fuck you.
That's right.
You're a false angel.
You're not even real.
Good night.
Keep peace for me.
See you later, nerd.
Oh, it's already open.
Well, in that case.
Wait, how am I going to get in there?
I can't hit it from here.
Ah, there we go.
Uh, you know what?
The light is kind of cool.
It's time for the chest room.
And then things happen.
Oh, wait, there's no area to get free items.
Okay, we got to save money now.
This is the money saving portion.
I should have done it a little bit earlier, but I was excited.
It happens.
Oh, my God.
Why do I have so many followers?
What the fuck is going on?
I mean, sure.
All right.
Cool.
I'm scared of holding the button.
FBI.
I need to see your teeth.
Come on.
Oh, God, that was close.
That was very close.
Oh, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
La, la, la, la, la, la.
Right.
That doesn't work like that.
That's a bit different.
Wait, we have a yellow flame now.
I can't even keep track.
This is getting out of hand.
Two keys at hand.
So that means we're gonna open a chest, I guess.
There's no other way.
Insane money situation.
So I wonder, am I just...
Maybe I wasn't just hitting it correctly, you know?
I don't know.
Wait, this just got cheaper.
Now it's only two.
Wait, is it five?
Oh, shit.
I think I may have just fucked it up.
Whoops.
That's on me.
It looked like a two.
Oh my god.
Holy damage.
Will you please just die?
There we go.
Spawn me my flies.
Spot, spot me.
Kai's.
He, he, he Kai's.
I can get in there.
I can fix it.
If I, if I, no, wait.
Blade safe.
What?
I can fly.
Yeah, I should have realized that.
This is gonna be hell.
Die!
Okay.
37 coins.
It's not bad.
We can do better.
Except I gotta go in here.
I gotta do this.
App sneaks.
I feel like I can't trust these coin numbers.
I'm not gonna buy anything, but I will use this so I can get more flies.
Nice.
There you are.
Oh god.
You're dead, son.
What?
Oh!
I see.
I did something risky there.
It didn't feel good.
Is that, that's an angel.
Angel style.
Angel is dead.
Dead sea scrolls.
Wait, what is the wizard thing?
Tears fire diagonally.
Oh, that's horrible.
Holy water.
Honestly, that's probably better for me.
I can line it up and then shoot them with the bombs.
Yeah.
This isn't active.
Wisp matches the item mimicked.
Huh.
That sounds interesting, actually.
But I need this.
I wonder how that's gonna work.
If I had the scrolls.
We're gonna fuck this guy up as well.
That's right, son.
Your ass is mine.
Key piece two.
So the question is, what do we do?
Unintentional rhyme.
I need health.
But maybe I don't.
Maybe it's okay.
Thanks.
I could also destroy this and re-roll things in case I wanted to.
I don't know if I want to.
Oh wait, this is a... Shit, yeah.
Okay.
See, I want to get flies, right?
That's the whole point.
We should look for secrets.
Maybe in here.
Yeah, just consume that for now.
Nice!
Oh wait, we found a secret already, though.
Whoops.
So many pills?
Yeah!
Okay, we buy a couple of these now.
That's it.
No more, I believe.
That is it.
I will restrain myself.
It's gonna be okay.
I can feel it in my bones.
Inside the marrow, there's a feeling there.
Oh wait, I'm shooting diagonally.
Okay, I'm not doing it anymore.
Money!
Spiders.
Oh god, you scared the crap out of me, man.
Look at that money, though!
Just in time for Christmas.
Thanks.
49.
Ultra grade shall die an ultra death.
Check out this damage, bro, son.
Oh god, you're not taking that money.
That's my money!
Where's my money, bitch?
Oh no, we got these people coming in.
The people are coming!
Fuck!
I don't have the optimal setup to deal with this situation.
I'm having trouble aiming.
Oh god, I shot myself.
Yeah, the holy water, baby!
Stand on the water!
Bantism!
Oh no, not this, not this, not this.
I'm dead, I'm dead.
No!
Fuck no way!
That's not happening!
We're done!
It's over.
I can't do this.
I got to lock in.
Ultimate locking in now.
No bullshit.
As soon as the doors open, I'm gonna go buck wild!
Like a bitch in heat.
That's a dog, by the way.
Fuck!
Come on!
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Open the doors!
Do it!
I dare you, I fucking dare you.
What the hell?
Stop spinning!
The door's opening!
That was horrible.
I knew that curse was gonna come back and bite me in the buttocks.
And what happened?
It bit me in the butt.
It felt good at first, but then it turned out it was painful.
Mm-hmm.
Not good.
What's up, guys?
That was a good attempt, though.
It wasn't even planned to do greed with that character.
It was supposed to be a normal run.
Like, I will say this, though, that last run was ultra-fun.
Despite the loss... I mean, the win would have been the cherry on top, right?
But it was just so much fun.
It was far from normal, you're right.
In fact, it's two difficulties away from normal.
There's heart and there's greed.
More like ultra rage bait.
I'm actually gonna ban that word from my channel soon.
And then you're gonna have to come up with a new one.
What are you gonna do then?
What are you gonna do with your lack of imagination?
Where's all the good jokes here?
Yeah, I'm gonna ban bait as well.
I'll ban anything that has anything to do with that.
Rage max... I like that one.
Okay.
Rage maxing, that's a good one.
Can we now make that normal?
I feel like that's a much better word.
Rage maxing is great.
Or bait maxing.
I like bait maxing too.
Oh man, anger mog... what is mogging?
I've heard that before.
What is mogging?
Bait max... yeah, bait.
Max...
they're baiting.
Good one, bro.
Please put some respect on Ludovico's name.
It had bad damage due to Eve not having a curse.
Nah, it sucks.
I don't buy that.
It's definitely terrible.
Right, guys?
Y'all agree with me.
It's a terrible item, right?
Tell him.
See?
Someone said yes.
There you go.
Well, anything is good on a Zazel, right?
You could give me, I don't know.
I don't know, like a rotten piece of meat on a Zazel and I will gladly take it because it will somehow make me invincible.
How do you feel about Ipekak?
I feel like it is good if you don't have the curse that makes you disappear from the room and you take damage while holding the charge button.
Then it's good.
Even with it, it's good.
I would say even with that curse, it's still good.
Like, did you see how much damage I did?
Well, how else would you pronounce Ipekak?
I'm curious about that.
Is there a way to pronounce Ipekak?
Ipekak, my reflection.
Ipekak.
Okay, I can say it like that too.
Ipekak?
That's one way to say it.
I would argue that's wrong.
I don't think that's correct.
You know what Ipekak is?
IRL?
Is it something about problem exists between user and keyboard?
Or like monitoring keyboard?
Or monitoring... I don't know, something like that.
Is it this continued drug that makes you vomit?
Oh no, that right, that's Ipekak.
Problem exists between keyboard?
I mean, where does it exist?
It's trying to say the user sucks, right?
Oh, chair!
Chair, of course.
Of course.
That's it.
Hope you're doing great.
I am doing great.
Thank you, blankie.
Are you doing okay?
Are you enjoying your Saturday?
Oh wait, it's not even Saturday.
Fuck me, dude.
Time is lying from me.
Why did I think it was Saturday?
I've been thinking it was Saturday all day today.
I can't believe that.
Huh.
Oh well, Sunday is not as great as Saturday, but it's still a good day.
My guess on data miner is it somehow duplicated my followers.
I don't know why or how, but it happened and then all of them shot bombs.
Other than that, anything weird that happened, probably data miner.
Reading is hard.
It is hard when you can't read it.
It's literally written in a foreign language.
Can you do a day of the week tier list?
I can do it right now.
S tier Friday, A tier Saturday.
No, Thursday because it's little Friday.
Saturday is definitely also A.
Sunday is B.
Rest is shit.
I poke whenever data miner shows up after that first data miner greed run.
Right?
I poke so hard when that happens, actually.
I'm not sure what poke means, but I do poke.
When Minecraft creates, I don't know.
At some point.
Maybe this year, maybe not.
It's definitely not in two years, is all I can say.
So it's before then.
But I don't know when.
Probably within one year, for sure.
Less than
a year.
I think it would be cool if you wrote tiny reviews on what you like this like on your website backlog.
I could.
It's also a lot of work, I guess, to sit in and write it.
And every time you write something like that down, you're just opening yourselves up to be attacked by random people on the internet for your opinions, right?
So on one side, yes, it's a great idea.
But in practice, it always turns to shit.
You know what I mean?
I can say bread is good.
And someone out there will be like, no, no, no, man.
Gluten and all that stuff will fuck you up long term.
You shouldn't eat bread.
It's terrible.
I can't believe you're doing this, you know?
Like you can't have an opinion on the internet.
But then again, I mean, I would say most people agree bread is good.
I despise bread.
Wow.
Damn.
To be honest, though, most of the bread they sell in supermarkets nowadays, I wouldn't even call it bread.
It's hyper-processed shit.
That is no good for your body.
Imagine having like gluten allergies where you can't even eat bread, man.
That sucks.
Like I seriously feel for those people.
I've had a friend that had that condition and it's just like, man, they can't eat anything.
It is crazy.
Subway bread was ruled by an Italian court to be candy, not bread.
Candy, though?
That's going a little far, isn't it?
Maybe in America where they put a lot of sugar in it.
You have allergies?
I have allergies right now.
But it's not for bread or any other food.
It's for the weather outside.
All the pollen is in the air.
It's really messing with me.
And it's only gonna get worse.
Other than that, I don't think I have an allergy.
Maybe a slight allergy to kiwis.
Because every time I eat them, my mouth goes tingling.
I also ate a whole pineapple once in one sitting because it was so tasty.
And I got such a big stomach ache from it.
But I think that's maybe just because I ate a whole pineapple.
I don't think I'm allergic to it.
I can't even imagine what it's like not to have allergies during the summer.
Imagine being able to go outside sniff the air without any issues.
You can enjoy the sun and the breeze on your face.
I can't even imagine.
That sounds like a fucking dream.
To me when I see the sun come out during summer and I see the weather you know like I'm just like that is like walking into Chernobyl.
It's crazy.
Yeah lucky you if you don't have any.
I envy you.
Yeah you should take it for granted I guess.
It's good.
Live your life in the best way.
Have you considered getting rid of your pollen algae?
I mean I've tried so many things man.
I've tried so many different medicines.
I'm close to just giving up on it and accepting it.
Maybe this year I'll try an injection for it.
But apparently that's not good for you.
Like some studies came out about that and apparently the Danish healthcare system does not recommend that you take those shots anymore for whatever reason.
I don't know I'm not a doctor.
But yeah.
It's your first year with pollen algae?
Man that sucks.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It's by a carton of pollen and snorted for two months straight and you'll be secured.
Is that actually true?
I mean I know you're being funny right?
But I know you can actually do stuff like that.
With certain things.
Like I saw a YouTube video of a girl who cured her gluten allergy or whatever it was called.
Gluten... you know.
What is it?
It's the stuff that's in milk I guess.
Whatever it was.
But she just drank like for a whole month.
Every day.
And she was sick for a whole month.
But then it went away.
Lactose intolerance.
That's the one.
Yes.
Yeah apparently not for everyone either.
But yeah it's crazy that that works.
Like once upon a time when I was younger I trained away my asthma that I had at the time.
I just you know trained that away by physical exercise.
So that happened.
I still have a bit of asthma now but that's related to Paulins.
Once again.
Different yeah.
I feel you Palicado.
I'm the same way.
I love lactose.
Dude I sometimes buy lactose just by itself you know.
Like in one of those I don't know is it half a liter?
Jugs or whatever?
And I just eat them with a spoon.
That's amazing dude.
But you gotta heat them up first of course.
My entire immune system runs on ginger shots.
Hey I should take more of those.
I'm kidding man.
I'm not eating that like that.
Come on.
I'm fucking with you.
Why you eat on your spoon?
Oh no.
I didn't even realize it sounded like that.
Oh my god.
That's even worse.
Oh shit.
Oh it's different from allergies?
Your body's missing enzymes needed to break lactate.
However, allergies are triggered by your immune system.
I guess.
But maybe the reactions you get are similar.
I'm not sure.
Your lactose intolerant is auntie.
Thankfully Finland has the best non lactose milk in the world.
Oh really?
Don't you also get like some extra money for the government or from the government when you have that?
At least in Denmark you do that.
Just because those lactose intolerant products are so much more expensive.
You get extra money from the government to buy it.
You don't?
I don't know what your prices are like over there though.
Lactose intolerant makes your shit yourself.
Rarely kills you on like allergies.
Right.
Okay.
Well I don't think pollen can kill you.
I mean anything is deadly in big amounts right?
Yeah some allergies can definitely kill you.
Like peanut allergies or nut allergies if you have like a crazy variety of that.
And you eat a lot of nuts you can die from that right?
It's the end of the stream Alsom.
Alsom 78.
I'm allergic to aging.
That sucks man.
Every time you have a birthday you have an outbreak.
Your whole face is you know swollen.
Yeah exactly Blue Baby.
Your airways get tightened until you can barely breathe.
I get that like maybe five or six times during each summer and I have like an inhalator to fix that.
Man the relief.
When you wake up in the middle of the night and you're like you can't breathe and you take that inhalator and it just opens it up and you can sort of breathe immediately.
It's the best feeling of all time.
It's so good.
I actually bought an air purifier once doggy bird.
Shit didn't work and it was a pretty expensive one too.
I ended up selling it again.
Like it's just not working.
What I need is a clean room.
I need to have NASA engineers come over here and engineer like precise clean rooms.
Less than one part per trillion pollen need to get inside.
Yeah I don't think mine was from Dyson.
It was from Coway I think.
Coway.
And it was advertised as you know it would... what was it?
Hepa whatever but also like allergy rated or something like that.
It should have worked is my point but maybe they were gamers.
You know you didn't buy it from me.
I would remember you.
Theoretically could nays just sterilize all the air inside the spacecraft so food doesn't spoil.
Oh NASA.
Well you wouldn't need to as long as you make sure the air is clean before you leave.
There's not gonna be any more new air right.
That's kind of the good thing about being enclosed in a small space.
Yeah it's the end of the stream my car.
I'm actually about to leave right now.
I good you reminded me.
Also for those that are liking Red Dead Redemption more of that tonight.
So you know that's coming up.
I plan to release more of that.
More regularly.
So thanks for watching guys and hanging out.
This was a great day of Isaac.
Lots of progress made.
Some unfortunate endings but progress nonetheless.
So all around good times.
I'll see you the next stream.
Bye bye.